<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mongoose Studios</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Mongoose Studios</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>example@test.com (Mongoose Studios)</managingEditor><webMaster>example@test.com (Mongoose Studios)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>LinkedOut</title><link>/posts/linked-out/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate><author>example@test.com (Mongoose Studios)</author><guid>/posts/linked-out/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="1-i-was-there-gandalf">1. I Was There, Gandalf&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Social media and I go back to the Myspace days. I don&amp;rsquo;t mean the sad corporate version it became after it was sold. I mean Myspace in all its early 2000s glory. Every page played music and most of them looked like someone was hosting a rave. &amp;ldquo;My Top 8&amp;rdquo; and who got added/removed or had their rank change was a new kind of gossip.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>It is Possible to Commit no Mistakes and Still Lose</title><link>/posts/commit-no-mistakes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate><author>example@test.com (Mongoose Studios)</author><guid>/posts/commit-no-mistakes/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="1-star-trek">1. Star Trek&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I grew up watching Star Trek: The Next Generation. It was one of those rare things that I could convince my parents to allow me to stay up to the very edge of my bedtime for. Like any young nerd in training I was there for the cool spaceships, the android, the aliens. The normal science fiction things that, I suspect, initially draw most of us to the genre. There were a lot of things that I didn&amp;rsquo;t appreciate back then, and not only because due to the vagaries of broadcast television and the episodic nature of the show making it hard to even conceive of, much less piece together, a grander story arc in my young brain.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 17:30:27 -0600</pubDate><author>example@test.com (Mongoose Studios)</author><guid>/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>Mongoose Studios is a creative venture trying to bring authenticity and serious long-form content back to the internet in the age of shorts with three different windows and an AI voiceover in them.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can watch me code live on &lt;a href="https://twitch.tv/mongoosestudios">Twitch&lt;/a> or on &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/@Mongoose_Studio">YouTube&lt;/a>. You can also follow me on &lt;a href="https://bsky.app/profile/mongoosestudios.bsky.social">BlueSky&lt;/a> where I mostly talk about painting tiny people, because all the software discussion has been swallowed by AI slop.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you would like to work with Mongoose Studios on a project, please &lt;a href="mailto:contact@mongoose.codes">email us&lt;/a> to discuss the specifics.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hello, World!</title><link>/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 17:16:01 -0600</pubDate><author>example@test.com (Mongoose Studios)</author><guid>/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>&lt;p>Famous first words, and important ones too. The traditional message to indicate that you have correctly configured
your environment and can proceed with the project that currently has your attention.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>How apropos, then, that this post exists to aid me in ensuring that all the machinery is in place and I can begin
this particular endeavor.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>