<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Mongoose Studios</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Mongoose Studios</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>example@test.com (Mongoose Studios)</managingEditor><webMaster>example@test.com (Mongoose Studios)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The only rules that really matter are these</title><link>/posts/cans-and-cannots/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate><author>example@test.com (Mongoose Studios)</author><guid>/posts/cans-and-cannots/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="1-savvy">1. Savvy?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The first Pirates of the Caribbean movie may well be peak Disney. It&amp;rsquo;s smart in the right places, silly in the right places, and Johnny Depp&amp;rsquo;s portrayal of a slightly unhinged and perpetually drunken pirate is absolutely brilliant for the tone of the movie. But in all that amusement there lies a quote that has stuck with me for the past 22 (yikes) years. &amp;ldquo;The only rules that really matter are these: what a man can do and what a man can&amp;rsquo;t do.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>LinkedOut</title><link>/posts/linked-out/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate><author>example@test.com (Mongoose Studios)</author><guid>/posts/linked-out/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="1-i-was-there-gandalf">1. I Was There, Gandalf&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Social media and I go back to the Myspace days. I don&amp;rsquo;t mean the sad corporate version it became after it was sold. I mean Myspace in all its early 2000s glory. Every page played music and most of them looked like someone was hosting a rave. &amp;ldquo;My Top 8&amp;rdquo; and who got added/removed or had their rank change was a new kind of gossip.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>It is Possible to Commit no Mistakes and Still Lose</title><link>/posts/commit-no-mistakes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate><author>example@test.com (Mongoose Studios)</author><guid>/posts/commit-no-mistakes/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="1-star-trek">1. Star Trek&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I grew up watching Star Trek: The Next Generation. It was one of those rare things that I could convince my parents to allow me to stay up to the very edge of my bedtime for. Like any young nerd in training I was there for the cool spaceships, the android, the aliens. The normal science fiction things that, I suspect, initially draw most of us to the genre. There were a lot of things that I didn&amp;rsquo;t appreciate back then, and not only because due to the vagaries of broadcast television and the episodic nature of the show making it hard to even conceive of, much less piece together, a grander story arc in my young brain.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hello, World!</title><link>/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 17:16:01 -0600</pubDate><author>example@test.com (Mongoose Studios)</author><guid>/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>&lt;p>Famous first words, and important ones too. The traditional message to indicate that you have correctly configured
your environment and can proceed with the project that currently has your attention.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>How apropos, then, that this post exists to aid me in ensuring that all the machinery is in place and I can begin
this particular endeavor.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>